<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Devin Carr</title><link>http://devincarr.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Devin Carr</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright Devin Carr © 2020</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://devincarr.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Year One</title><link>http://devincarr.com/posts/year-one/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://devincarr.com/posts/year-one/</guid><description>This is a short recounting of my first year as a software developer working on conflation for Bing Maps at Microsoft. Much of this will most likely be common knowledge to senior developers, but I wanted to share my personal views and provide a reference for some colleagues who will be entering the workforce soon.</description></item><item><title>Exoplanet Discovery via Gravitational Microlensing</title><link>http://devincarr.com/posts/exoplanet-discovery/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://devincarr.com/posts/exoplanet-discovery/</guid><description>Gravitational microlensing is the influence of a stellar body on the light from a further visible body. This phenomena can be used to discover small exoplanets orbiting around a stellar body that passes in front of another visible light source. These small planets are in the range of a Super-Earth: 15-17 Earth masses.</description></item><item><title>Suggest</title><link>http://devincarr.com/posts/suggest/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://devincarr.com/posts/suggest/</guid><description>A simple commandline tool to provide auto suggestions via Bing Autosuggest API.
The Github if you would like to try it out!
Inspiration I found something similar the other day on HackerNews, but it used Google's auto-complete API. Since I will be joining the Bing team soon, I decided to see if Bing has an open API that can do the same thing.</description></item><item><title>Echo: A Twitch.tv Chat Bot</title><link>http://devincarr.com/posts/echo-a-chat-bot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://devincarr.com/posts/echo-a-chat-bot/</guid><description>When I first thought up the idea for echo, I proposed it to a good friend of mine. He cautioned me, mentioning that, &amp;ldquo;it could be used for good or for evil.&amp;rdquo; He wasn't wrong..
Echo is just your average irc connected chat bot hooked up to the ever growing Twitch.</description></item><item><title>Finishing personal projects</title><link>http://devincarr.com/posts/learning-to-complete/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://devincarr.com/posts/learning-to-complete/</guid><description>A new idea or project always seems to come to mind, sometimes during the middle of another project. The new idea or concept in my mind always forces me to follow a set of stages to understand or flesh out the idea.</description></item><item><title>Information Extraction on Research Papers</title><link>http://devincarr.com/posts/information-extraction/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://devincarr.com/posts/information-extraction/</guid><description>Research papers provide a wonderful data set to work with as they provide a diverse set of terms and complex abstraction of common knowledge. I was interested in trying to relate a large set of research papers by their concepts as an easy form of tagging/indexing.</description></item><item><title>Robot Locality within a Pipeline</title><link>http://devincarr.com/posts/robot-university-project/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://devincarr.com/posts/robot-university-project/</guid><description>Situation A small robot needs to travel down a pipeline around 18 inches in diameter. It will be powered by battery alone and cannot be communicated once within the pipe. My task is to construct a method to allow it to travel down the pipe in a straight line.</description></item></channel></rss>